All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
That is my army.
30,000 slaves we've captured this month.
All human, too.
And then there's 70,000 Fishmen, trained in combat.
They're all from the Fishman district.
Or can't you tell?
Now behold, 100,000 United Outlaws!
You see, this is power!
Because my followers have faith in change!
It's taken 10 years, but it's time that we finished what I began so long ago!
And you know what started it?
The death of Queen Otohime!
Yes, that's right!
I've got a little secret.
Wanna hear?
The one who shot her...
was Mei!
That can't be true!
Even in her death, your mother changed the island by turning the humans into villains once more.
And yet, it wasn't them.
No, it was her own subject!
The Fishman standing in front of you!
I did it!
I killed her!
Because it was necessary!
I knew you did it!
Shirohoshi!
What did you say?
Shirohoshi's tears!
Muffy finally shows up!
You already knew that I murdered your mother.
How can that be?
Explain yourself right now, Shirohoshi!
Our father!
Are you alright?
Stay strong!
Shirohoshi!
A few years after Mother's death, Megalo told me in secret about everything that happened.
Megalo?
He told you?
Tell me it isn't true!
Are you sure?
Oh, no!
At the time, Megalo was the property of Neptune's army.
And he witnessed the incident with his own eyes.
Mother, no!
Mother!
Come on!
Oh, no!
There was nothing!
You knew all of this, and yet you never told a soul?
How could I?
If I did, I was afraid that our countrymen might hold a grudge against Horty.
And that is not what my dear mother would have wanted.
That was the final promise we made to her as she lied dying.
She said that no matter who it was who took her life,
we should not be angry or let our hearts be filled with hatred.
It doesn't matter who did this to me.
Don't become angry, not on my behalf.
Don't submit to resentment.
Don't let hatred get the better of you.
Not in my name or any other.
Shirahoshi, so that was why...
All these years, and not a word!
Our mother's final wish, you've kept it deep in your heart until today.
Closed in the hardshell tower, you've carried this burden all alone.
Your foolish brother's blissfully ignorant.
She suffered in silence, even knowing that her mother's killer ran free.
Despite my loyalty to the queen, I could not fathom such forgiveness.
I would not have the strength to keep my word.
And yet, she was true to her oath.
You truly honor your mother's legacy, princess.
Stop laughing, you fool!
I can't help it!
This is downright comical!
And...
Megalo!
There was nothing to stop you from shouting to the top of your lungs that day,
and letting everyone know I was the one responsible for killing Otohime.
So thank you for keeping your mouth shut,
and for choosing this pathetic fool of a girl as the one and only keeper of your little secret.
If you told anyone else about it, we never would have been able to make it this far.
Convenient though it was.
Where I come from, we call actions like yours idiotic.
Your kingdom is about to fall, and all because of some meaningless promise to a dead woman.
Sure, you honored her words, but now you, your family, and your subjects are all going to die.
I hope it was worth it, Shira Horshi.
Pay that murderer no heed, your majesty.
Believe me, you have done nothing wrong.
Not wrong, just incredibly stupid.
Shark arrows!
He's gonna kill them!
Stop this!
Please, no!
Don't hurt them! I beg you!
Look at that! Pathetic!
No! We're doomed!
They're the great warriors? Yeah, right!
We crushed them like a bunch of worms!
The captain made quick work of them, didn't he?
They won't even make it to the execution if you ask me!
Well, we can't have that. The royal family should face death by beheading, after all.
Now, someone hand me a sword.
Our only concerns were Jinbei and Shirahoshi.
Now that they're here, there's no reason we can't kick off this execution right now.
At long last, these foul vermin known as the royal family will be slaughtered by my hand!
All right! Off with the heads!
Yeah!
Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now!
Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them now! Kill them!
Charlie!
Kill them now!
Children!
Hey!
When is that pirate with the hat coming?
He was gonna destroy the island, right?
Well?
When is he coming?
Kill them now!
I honestly couldn't tell you.
The only thing I can see is what will happen in the future.
I simply have no way of discerning when.
I want him to come now.
Kill them now!
If he comes here and tries to start a fight right now,
we might be in trouble.
But so will the bad guys.
He has to show up!
Cause if he doesn't, that man is gonna kill King Neptune!
Where is he?
You're exactly right, children.
That pirate is our only hope.
Hey!
Straw Hat Lurie!
If you want to destroy this island, go ahead!
Hurry up!
Tear this place to pieces!
We don't care!
Straw Hat!
I know you're out there somewhere!
If you're close enough to hear us, come and fight!
Please hurry!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! Straw Hat! Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Wretched fools. If that's their only hope, then they're better off dead. As far as I know, Shali's premonitions have always been reliable, but I'll be damned if this one comes true.
It's meaningless folly.
Perhaps I should bring these desperate worms back to their senses.
Listen, you morons! It's time for the dawning of our new era!
So say goodbye to your king!
No, stop!
Watch carefully, everyone! This is history in the making, after all!
It's not every day you see a king's head roam.
This mediocre ruler of yours without a drop of pride for his own race will be no more!
And the new kingdom of fishmen will rise up to conquer those miserable humans, as we were meant to do from the start!
Now witness the demise of the Ryugu kingdom, once and for all!
I've failed.
Farewell!
Luffy!
Luffy?!
Police?
I need you!
Save my father!
Harry!
Henry!
Harry! Harry!
Megalo?
Yeah!
Hmm?
It can't be!
It is!
It's Small Hat Luffy!
I can't believe it!
He really did show up!
Whoa! Did you see that?
He just saved King Neptune's life!
Yeah! Maybe he's okay!
I mean, Princess Shirohoshi did call him for help, right?
Please help me!
Wait, he was in the shark?
Ah! Hiding in its stomach, it looks like!
That's gross!
Luffy! I thought I told you to wait!
But I suppose there was no choice, was there?
Come out! All of you, right now!
Luffy! What does he mean?
I don't see anybody here!
We were prepared for this from the beginning.
See, the plan was for Luffy to sit tight and wait a while.
But it's Luffy!
So that wasn't happening!
Mirage, release!
Ah! Where'd you come from?
You scared me!
Is this it? The letter from the Celestial Dragons?
That's it! Excellent work!
But it's right!
Hey! The letter's gone! How'd she get it?
How in the hell could you let that happen?
Oh, and I gave the key to Robin!
But it's right here!
It's gone too!
That's what you get for yelling at me, jerk!
Hey, we're free!
Who did that?
It's Robin!
What?
Please, stay with us, Father! Look up in the sky! What is that?
Unbelievable!
It's a whale and... a lion? No, wait, that's... a ship!
Don't kill me!
It's aiming right at us!
Fire!
Windy...
Fire.
Fire!
That whale's escaping with the royal family!
Dammit!
They'll catch you and make you pray!
Huh? What happened, my son?
I can't say for certain, but it would appear that Jinbei's made some sort of plan with the Straw Hats.
I don't believe it! Straw Hat actually came! That's his crew! There, look!
Oh wow, that's a pretty big crowd they've got.
This is nuts! What, are we fighting a whole army now?
I guess so. Looks like about 80,000 guys. No, 100,000 maybe.
Not a bare-bones operation, then.
You might as well go take a nap, Curly Brows. I can handle these chumps.
Aren't naps your thing?
Well, this ought to be pretty fun. And there's plenty of hats to kick, so let's party!
Look! It's the rest of the Straw Hats! They're getting off the ship!
Hey! Straw Hat Luffy! Are you guys really planning on destroying Fishman Island?
Why did you take over the Ryugu Palace? Did you want to kill the royal family yourselves?
Were you the ones who kidnapped the mermaids? Answer me!
Come on, Straw Hat! The least you can do is say something!
Are you guys supposed to be our friends or our enemies?
Explain yourself, Straw Hat!
Friends or enemies, huh? Don't ask me.
Cause I'd say, it's up to you!
After a tricky escape from the Ryugu Palace, the Straw Hats have reassembled at last.
As they march into Conchcord Plaza, an army of new Fishman Pirates stands before them.
The final battle of the fate of Fishman Island begins with a show of strength between the two would-be kings.
On the next One Piece! A big clash! The Straw Hats versus a hundred thousand enemies! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
the
Attack! The